<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GDG</string>
    <string name="heading">theFive</string>
    <string name="FireHeat">Fire Heat</string>

    <string name="air_des" formatted="false">
        The atmosphere of Earth is the layer of gases, commonly known as air, that surrounds the planet Earth and is
        retained by Earth\'s gravity. The atmosphere protects life on Earth by absorbing ultraviolet solar radiation,
        warming the surface through heat retention (greenhouse effect), and reducing temperature extremes between day
        and night (the diurnal temperature variation).

        By volume, dry air contains 78.09% nitrogen, 20.95% oxygen, 0.93% argon, 0.039% carbon dioxide, and small
        amounts of other gases. Air also contains a variable amount of water vapor, on average around 1% at sea level,
        and 0.4% over the entire atmosphere. Air content and atmospheric pressure vary at different layers, and air
        suitable for use in photosynthesis by terrestrial plants and breathing of terrestrial animals is found only in
        Earth\'s troposphere and in artificial atmospheres.

        The atmosphere has a mass of about 5.15×1018 kg, three quarters of which is within about 11 km of the surface.
        The atmosphere becomes thinner and thinner with increasing altitude, with no definite
        boundary between the atmosphere and outer space. The Kármán line, at 100 km, or 1.57% of Earth\'s radius,
        is often used as the border between the atmosphere and outer space. Atmospheric effects become noticeable during
        atmospheric reentry of spacecraft at an altitude of around 120 km. Several layers can be distinguished
        in the atmosphere, based on characteristics such as temperature and composition.
    </string>


    <string name="fire_des">
        Fire is the rapid oxidation of a material in the exothermic chemical process of combustion, releasing heat,
        light, and various reaction products. Slower oxidative processes like rusting or digestion are not included
        by this definition.
        
        Fire is hot because conversion of the weak double bond in molecular oxygen, O2, to the stronger bonds in the
        combustion products carbon dioxide and water releases energy (418 kJ per 32 g of O2); the bond energies of the
        fuel play only a minor role here. At a certain point in the combustion reaction, called the ignition point,
        flames are produced. The flame is the visible portion of the fire. Flames consist primarily of carbon dioxide,
        water vapor, oxygen and nitrogen. If hot enough, the gases may become ionized to produce plasma. Depending on
        the substances alight, and any impurities outside, the color of the flame and the fires intensity will be
        different.
    </string>


    <string name="water_des" formatted="false">
        Water (chemical formula: H2O) is a transparent fluid which forms the world\'s streams, lakes, oceans and rain,
        and is the major constituent of the fluids of organisms. As a chemical compound, a water molecule contains one
        oxygen and two hydrogen atoms that are connected by covalent bonds. Water is a liquid at standard ambient
        temperature and pressure, but it often co-exists on Earth with its solid state, ice; and gaseous state, steam
        (water vapor). It also exists as snow, fog, dew and cloud.

        Water covers 71% of the Earth\'s surface. It is vital for all known forms of life. On Earth, 96.5% of the
        planet\'s crust water is found in seas and oceans, 1.7% in groundwater, 1.7% in glaciers and the ice caps of
        Antarctica and Greenland, a small fraction in other large water bodies, and 0.001% in the air as vapor, clouds
        (formed of ice and liquid water suspended in air), and precipitation. Only 2.5% of this water is
        freshwater, and 98.8% of that water is in ice (excepting ice in clouds) and groundwater. Less than 0.3% of all
        freshwater is in rivers, lakes, and the atmosphere, and an even smaller amount of the Earth\'s freshwater
        (0.003%) is contained within biological bodies and manufactured products. A greater quantity of water is
        found in the earth\'s interior.
    </string>


    <string name="earth_des" formatted="false">
        Earth (otherwise known as The World) is the third planet
        from the Sun, the densest planet in the Solar System, the largest of the Solar System\'s four terrestrial
        planets, and the only astronomical object known to harbor life.

        According to radiometric dating and other sources of evidence, Earth was formed about 4.54 billion years
        ago. Earth gravitationally interacts with other objects in space, especially the Sun and the Moon.
        During one orbit around the Sun, Earth rotates about its own axis 366.26 times, creating 365.26 solar days or
        one sidereal year. Earth\'s axis of rotation is tilted 23.4° away from the perpendicular of its orbital
        plane, producing seasonal variations on the planet\'s surface with a period of one tropical year (365.24 solar
        days). The Moon is Earth\'s only permanent natural satellite. Its gravitational interaction with Earth causes
        ocean tides, stabilizes the orientation of Earth\'s rotational axis, and gradually slows Earth\'s rotational
        rate.
    </string>


    <string name="space_des">
        Space is the boundless three-dimensional extent in which objects and events have relative position and
        direction. Physical space is often conceived in three linear dimensions, although modern physicists usually
        consider it, with time, to be part of a boundless four-dimensional continuum known as spacetime. The concept of
        space is considered to be of fundamental importance to an understanding of the physical universe.
    </string>
</resources>
